export const trivia = {

  Questions: [
    {
      Question:
      "C is the father of D but D is not the son of C. How is that possible?",
      Choices: [
        "D is C's daughter",
        "C is D's uncle",
        "They  are not related",
        "D is C's nephew",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "D is C's daughter",
    },

    {
      Question:
      "What is the only body part that is fully grown from birth?",
      Choices: [
        "Nose",
        "Eyes",
        "Ears",
        "Jaw",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Eyes",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "Before Mount Everest was discovered, what was the highest mountain on earth?",
      Choices: [
        "Mt. Vesuvius",
        "Mt. Everest",
        "Mt. Carmel",
        "Mt. Mckinley",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Mt. Everest",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "If Peacocks do not lay eggs, how are baby peacocks born?",
      Choices: [
        "Live birth",
        "in labs",
        "They are born from an older peacock's ashes",
        "Peahens have them",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Peahens have them",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "Which is heavier, 100 pounds of steel or 100 pounds of feathers?",
      Choices: [
        "Steel",
        "Feathers",
        "They weigh the same",
        "Neither weighs 100 pounds",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "They weigh the same",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "How many months have 28 days?",
      Choices: [
        "1",
        "None",
        "3",
        "All",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "All",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "How many times can you subtract 5 from 40?",
      Choices: [
        "1",
        "6",
        "4",
        "2",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "1",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "A truck driver goes down a one-way street the wrong way in front of cops.Why is he not pulled over?",
      Choices: [
        "It was opposite day",
        "He was walking",
        "His truck was blue",
        "He was very short",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "He was walking",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "How many pears can you put in an empty basket?",
      Choices: [
        "0",
        "1",
        "15",
        "need more info to answer that",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "1",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "A rooster lays an egg on a barn roof,which way does it roll?",
      Choices: [
        "to the left",
        "to the right",
        "up",
        "It doesn't",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "It doesn't",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "You are in a dark room with a candle, a gas stove and a lamp. You only have one match.Which do you light first?",
      Choices: [
        "the Stove",
        "the Lamp",
        "the Match",
        "the Candle",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "the Match",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "Lake Geneva is in which state?",
      Choices: [
        "Missouri",
        "Switzerland",
        "liquid",
        "gas",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Liquid",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "How long is a fortnight?",
      Choices: [
        "4 days",
        "15 days",
        "12 days",
        "21 days",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "21 days",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "It's Saturday morning and your grandmother sends you to the bakery for a baker's dozen croissants. How many croissants does she expect you to return with?",
      Choices: [
        "10",
        "12",
        "13",
        "The bakery doesn't open on weekends",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "13",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "A farmer has 17 cows; all but six die. How many cows does the farmer have left?",
      Choices: [
        "0",
        "6",
        "7",
        "11",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "6",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "What is the chemical symbol for potassium?",
      Choices: [
        "P",
        "Pt",
        "Po",
        "K",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "K",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "If a peanut falls from a tree when the wind is lightly blowing south, where is it most likely to land?",
      Choices: [
        "It will go with the wind-south",
        "Peanuts doesn't grow on trees",
        "Gravity would drop it straight down",
        "A peanut is heavy enough to go against the wind-north",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Peanuts doesn't grow on trees",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "You're on fire!!! What do you do?",
      Choices: [
        "Call 911",
        "Panic",
        "Shout for help",
        "Stop, drop and roll",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Stop, drop and roll",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "Prince is on a sick bed in the hospital. THe nurse enters and says while pointing to Peter, 'That's my son'. But the nurse is not Prince's mum. Who then is the nurse?",
      Choices: [
        "His Sister",
        "His Stepmum",
        "His Dad",
        "Nobody",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "His Dad",
    }, 

    {
      Question:
      "John's father has three kids namely Prince and Paul. What's the name of the third kid?",
      Choices: [
        "Peter",
        "Pontious",
        "I don't know",
        "John",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "John",
    }
  ]
}